{
 "quiz2": [
 {
    "id" : 1,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java is the second most popular language?",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 2,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "The original name for Java was Oak.",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 3,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java is said to have been created on purpose.",
    "correctAnswer" : "false",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 4,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "In Java the meaning  of the final keyword is final",
    "correctAnswer" : "false",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 5,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java is used by 95% of the enterprises as their primary language.",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 6,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "How many times does Java get downloaded in one year?",
    "correctAnswer" : "One billion",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 7,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What was the name of the team of engineers who developed Java?",
    "correctAnswer" : "Green team",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 8,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "The process of assigning a value to a variable is___________",
    "correctAnswer" : "initialization",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 9,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "A class that implements a table, which maps keys to values.",
    "correctAnswer" : "Hash table",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 10,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What year was Java initiated?",
    "correctAnswer" : "1991",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 11,
    "questionType" : "multiple_choice",
    "questionText" : "Which name is a actual type of Loop in Java?",
    "options": ["for-loop", "switch-loop", "modal-loop", "script-loop"],
    "correctAnswer" : "for-loop",
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 12,
    "questionType" : "multiple_choice",
    "questionText" : "What is considered a blueprint which describes methods, functions, and constructors Java?",
    "options":  ["Function", "Project", "Class", "Object"],
    "correctAnswer" : "Class",
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 13,
    "questionType" : "multiple_choice",
    "questionText" : "What is the definition of encapsulation?",
    "options":  ["Wrapping data in a single unit", "Wrapping data into two units", "Wrapping data into four units", "Wrapping data into three units"],
    "correctAnswer" : "Wrapping data in a single unit",
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 14,
    "questionType" : "multiple_choice",
    "questionText" : "When classes have the same name but have many different functions it is called _________",
    "options": ["Declaration", "Polymorphism", "Initialization", "Compiling"],
    "correctAnswer" : "Polymorphism",
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 15,
    "questionType" : "multiple_choice",
    "questionText" : "What is the name of transferring properties from one class to another?",
    "options": ["Networking", "Sharing", "Data-Abstraction", "Inheritance"],
    "correctAnswer" : "Inheritance",
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 16,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java has a access modifier named Private.",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 17,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java's power comes from the ability to compile code that can be read on any computer that has the Java Virtual Machine installed.",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 18,
    "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Properly written Java programs execute slowly and uses lots of memory.",
    "correctAnswer" : "false",
    "options" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 19,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "________ is automatically handled by Java Virtual Machine, which means the programmer does not need to write code to manage memory.",
    "correctAnswer" : "Memory Management",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
   {
    "id" : 20,
    "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "A placeholder for a value which can be modified according to the needs of the program or the results of a calculation is called a ______",
    "correctAnswer" : "variable",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
    "feedback": ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  }
  
  
  
  
]
}
